# Elizer A. Bachanicha Jr.

Develop Web applications for more than two years using performant technologies .Net Core and Vue JS

Have a teachable spirit and always open to learn new things, especially on development good practices. Seeking to become part of a team where I can learn and grow professionally.



Full-stack Web developer

https://bachelizer.github.io/

Email: bachanichaelizer@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizer-bachanicha-050027224

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/bachelizer/">https://github.com/bachelizer/</a>

Mobile No. +639187714627 / +639455923183

### Tools and Technologies

HTML

CSS

Javascript































Bootstrap, .Net Core , Vue, Javascript, Vuetify, Mysql, FastReport, Dapper ORM, Typescript, Git versioning control, Github

laravel, React, Firebase, Tailwind CSS

# Work Experience

#### Full Stack Web Developer (Full-time)

2020 – Present

Agusan del Sur State College of Agriculture and Technology

#### **Duties and Responsibilities**

- Build Web applications from concept through deployment
- Design and create Database
- Design and Analyze System flow that meets System Requirements
- Implement front-end responsive and mobile-first approach strategy
- Create transactional SQL queries, stored procedures, triggers, and events
- Develop back-end and optimize performance

#### Front-end Developer (Part-time)

February 2022 - July 2022

ZEA Informatique Inc.

#### **Duties and Responsibilities**

- Develop front-end using Vue and Material Design Framework
  Vuetify keeping the mobile-first approach strategy
- Using Firebase for data storage
- Using Google Map API to Integrate data

#### IT Specialist (Full-time)

2018 – 2020

Bayugan City Doctors Hospital

#### **Duties and Responsibilities**

- System Administration
- SQL queries for checking data integrity and data troubleshooting
- Using Photoshop Software for Graphic Designing
- Software and Hardware Troubleshooting

## Education

#### Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

2018

Agusan del Sur State College of Agriculture and Technology San Teodoro, Bunawan, Agusan del Sur, Philippines